Inventory of the Dora and Cara Armistead Papers 1880-1950
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Dora and Cara Armistead Papers 1880-1950
Special Collections Research Center
01/Mss. Acc. 2004.24, 2006.54
6.00
Papers from the household of Dora Travis Armistead (1890-1979) and Rowland Cara Armistead, sisters of Williamsburg, Virginia. Includes letters, personal, financial and business papers of Cary Peyton Armistead (1856-1901), father of Dora and Cara, Steward of Eastern Lunatic Asylum (now Eastern State Hospital), and prominent local Episcopal Church and school leader; Eudora Ester Armistead (d. 1940), mother; Cary Champion Armistead (d. 1944), brother, and lawyer for a time in Detroit, Michigan; Meriwether Irving Armistead (d. 1945), brother, and lawyer in Williamsburg; and Dora and Cara Armistead, elementary school teachers; along with materials related to relatives in the Armistead family, most notably Gregory Armistead, brother, who died at an early age; and Julia Maria Armistead (1858-1897), sister of Cary Peyton. The papers pertain primarily to Armistead family finances, health and personal affairs, the financial operation of the asylum/hospital, and school and church issues. Also included are a number of undated and unlabeled photographs, schoolwork of the Armistead siblings as children and college students, letters to Cary Peyton from College of William and Mary Presidents Benjamin S. Ewell and Lyon G. Tyler, and a long series of letters to Cary Champion from girlfriend Ruth Conkey.
Armistead, Dora Travis, 1890-1979; Armistead Family; Armistead, Cary Champion, d. 1944; Armistead, Cary Peyton, 1856-1901; Armistead, Gregory; Armistead, Maria, 1858-1897; Armistead, Meriwether Irving, d. 1945; Armistead, Rowland Cara; Conkey, Ruth; Ewell, Benjamin Stoddert; Tyler, Lyon Gardiner, 1853-1935 arrangement
Administrative Information
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
The materials were acquired by Special Collections Research Center from Hamilton's Bookstore. on 00/00/2006.
Biographical Note
Information about this individual or organization may be available in the Special Collections Research Center Wiki: http://scrc.swem.wm.edu/wiki/index.php/Dora Travis Armistead
Scope and Contents
Papers from the household of Dora Travis Armistead (1890-1979) and Rowland Cara Armistead, sisters of Williamsburg, Virginia. Includes letters, personal, financial and business papers of Cary Peyton Armistead (1856-1901), father of Dora and Cara, Steward of Eastern Lunatic Asylum (now Eastern State Hospital), and prominent local Episcopal Church and school leader; Eudora Ester Armistead (d. 1940), mother; Cary Champion Armistead (d. 1944), brother, and lawyer for a time in Detroit, Michigan; Meriwether Irving Armistead (d. 1945), brother, and lawyer in Williamsburg; and Dora and Cara Armistead, elementary school teachers; along with materials related to relatives in the Armistead family, most notably Gregory Armistead, brother, who died at an early age; and Julia Maria Armistead (1858-1897), sister of Cary Peyton. The papers pertain primarily to Armistead family finances, health and personal affairs, the financial operation of the asylum/hospital, and school and church issues. Also included are a number of undated and unlabeled photographs, schoolwork of the Armistead siblings as children and college students, letters to Cary Peyton from College of William and Mary Presidents Benjamin S. Ewell and Lyon G. Tyler, and a long series of letters to Cary Champion from girlfriend Ruth Conkey.
Additional Information
Index Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Blackstone Female Institute (Va.); The Model School (Williamsburg, Va.)
Genre/Form of Material:
Certificates; Correspondence; Financial records; Photographs
Geographic Name:
Confederate Memorial (Williamsburg, Va.); Williamsburg (Va.)--History--19th century.; Williamsburg (Va.)--History--20th century.
Personal Name:
Charles, John S., 1851-1930
Topical Term:
College of William and Mary--History--20th century.; Eastern State Hospital (Va.)--History.; Episcopal Church--Virginia--Clergy--20th century.; Lawyers--Virginia--Correspondence.; Women--Education--Virginia.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Mss. Acc. 2006.54, 1880-1950; id60351
  - Finances, id60695
    - Cary Armistead Finances, id60696 (Box 1)
      - Undated Bills and Receipts. 69 items., id60697 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - Undated Bills and Receipts. 69 items, id60698 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - 1881 to 1884 Receipts and Bills. 23 items, id60699 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 2)
        - 1885 Receipts and Bills. 23 items, id60700 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 3)
        - 1886 Receipts and Bills. 7 items, id60701 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 4)
        - 1887 Receipts and Bills. 10 items, id60702 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 5)
        - 1888 Receipts and Bills. 30 items, id60703 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 6)
        - 1889 Receipts and Bills. 38 items, id60704 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 7)
        - 1890 Receipts and Bills (Part 1). 54 items, id60705 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 8)
        - 1890 Receipts and Bills (Part 2). 45 items, id60706 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 9)
        - 1891 Receipts and Bills. 45 items, id60707 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 10)
        - 1892 Receipts and Bills. 43 items, id60708 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 11)
        - 1893 Receipts and Bills. 25 items, id60709 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 12)
        - 1894 Receipts and Bills. 26 items, id60710 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 13)
        - 1895 Receipts and Bills. 22 items, id60711 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 14)
        - 1896 Receipts and Bills. 20 items, id60712 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 15)
        - 1897 Receipts and Bills. 22 items, id60713 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 16)
        - 1898 Receipts and Bills. 18 items, id60714 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 17)
        - 1899 Receipts and Bills. 15 items, id60715 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 18)
        - 1900 to 1901 Receipts and Bills. 30 items, id60716 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 19)
        - Cancelled Checks and Bank Receipts. 101 items, id60717 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 20)
        - Insurance and Investment Pamphlets. 10 items, id60718 (Box 1, Folder 1, Folder 21)
      - 1881 to 1884 Receipts and Bills. 23 items., id61630 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1885 Receipts and Bills. 23 items., id61631 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1886 Receipts and Bills. 7 items., id61632 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1887 Receipts and Bills. 10 items., id61633 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1888 Receipts and Bills. 30 items., id61634 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1889 Receipts and Bills. 38 items., id61635 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1890 Receipts and Bills (Part 1). 54 items, id61636 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1890 Receipts and Bills (Part 2). 45 items., id61637 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Armistead Family Finances, id60719 (Box 2)
      - id60720 (Box 2)
        - Family Tax Materials, 1919 to 1945. 18 items, id60721 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - Family Account Books. 2 items, id60722 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Family Account Books. 1 item, id60723 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Tax and Health Permits for Armistead Guest House Operation, 1962 to 1974. 10 items, id60724 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Dora (I) Armistead Banking Papers and Receipts. 111 items, id60725 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - Cara Armistead Receipts. 72 items, id60726 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Cara Armistead Banking Papers. 15 items, id60727 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - Cara Armistead Cancelled Checks. 78 items, id60728 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Champ Armistead Receipts. 29 items, id60729 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Champ Armistead Banking Papers. 27 items, id60730 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - Champ Armistead Banking Papers. 248 items, id60731 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - Meriwether Armistead Receipts. 4 items, id60732 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - Dora (II) Armistead Bills. 3 items, id60733 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - Julia Armistead Finances. 2 items, id60734 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Family Tax Materials, 1919 to 1945. 18 items., id62004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Family Account Books. 2 items., id62005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Family Account Books. 1 item., id62006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Tax and Health Permits for Armistead Guest House Operation, 1962 to 1974. 10 items., id62007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Dora (I) Armistead Banking Papers and Receipts. 111 items., id62008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Cara Armistead Receipts. 72 items., id62009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Cara Armistead Banking Papers. 15 items., id62010 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Cara Armistead Cancelled Checks. 78 items., id62011 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Champ Armistead Receipts. 29 items., id62012 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Champ Armistead Banking Papers. 27 items., id62013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Champ Armistead Banking Papers. 248 items., id62014 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Meriwether Armistead Receipts. 4 items., id62015 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Dora (II) Armistead Bills. 3 items., id62016 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Julia Armistead Finances. 2 items., id62017 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Dora (I) Armistead Cancelled Checks, 1902 – 1918; id61610 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, id61611
    - Family Correspondence. Armistead Family Letters and Correspondence., id62071 (Box 9)
      - Dora (I) Armistead’s Correspondence – Undated. 6 items., id62144 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Dora (I) Armistead’s Correspondence – 1890 to 1909. 11 items., id62145 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Dora (I) Armistead’s Correspondence – 1910 to 1939. 6 items., id62146 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Dora (II) Armistead’s Correspondence. 12 items., id62147 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Cara Armistead’s Correspondence. 24 items., id62148 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Meriwether Armistead’s Business Correspondence. 11 items., id62149 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Meriwether Armistead’s Christmas Cards. 8 items., id62150 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Meriwether Armistead’s Christmas Cards. 8 items., id62151 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Letter Fragments, Undated. 18 items., id62152 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Letters to Unknown and Unrecognized Recipients. 23 items., id62153 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Registered Mail Receipts. 3 items., id62154 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Emily Waltrip’s Correspondence. 8 items., id62155 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Armistead Family Letters and Correspondence., id61612 (Sub-series 1)
    - Correspondence from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, id61613 (Sub-series 2)
      - Armistead Family Letters and Correspondence., id62018 (Sub-series 2, Box 4)
        - Champ Armistead Correspondence – Business and Employment-Related. 9 items., id62019 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 1)
        - Champ Armistead Correspondence with Friends. 22 items., id62020 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 2)
        - Champ Armistead Correspondence with Hazel/”Carolina”. Note that Hazel – last name unknown – is occasionally referred to in these letters as “Carolina.” 9 items., id62021 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 3)
        - Champ Armistead Correspondence with Margaret [perhaps Tyler], Virgie [last name unknown], Dick Lawson, and Copie [last name unknown]. 21 items., id62022 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence among Armistead Family Members, undated. 14 items., id62023 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence among Armistead Family Members, 1885 to 1895. 11 items., id62024 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence among Armistead Family Members, 1896 to 1899. 17 items., id62025 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence among Armistead Family Members, 1900 to 1940. 15 items., id62026 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence among Armistead Family Members, 1941 to 1944. 9 items., id62027 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 9)
        - orrespondence Between Meriwether and Dora (II) Regarding the Addition of a Bathroom to the Family Home. 10 items., id62028 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 10)
        - Empty Envelopes. 74 items., id62029 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 11)
        - Empty Envelopes. 72 items., id62030 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 12)
        - Empty Envelopes. 75 items., id62031 (Sub-series 2, Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead. The letters in this box, and the next two, were written by a friend and admirer, Ruth Conkey, whom Champ met during his time at the College of William and Mary. The correspondence continued for four years from 1919 to 1922, as Champ moved from Williamsburg to Wilmington, Del., and then Detroit, Mich. Letters are arranged chronologically by date., id62032 (Sub-series 2, Box 5)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, May 1 through May 20, 1919. 11 items., id62033 (Sub-series 2, Box 5, Folder 1)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, May 21 through May 31, 1919. 12 items., id62034 (Sub-series 2, Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, May 21 through May 31, 1919. 12 items., id62035 (Sub-series 2, Box 5, Folder 3)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, July 1, through July 13, 1919. 8 items., id62036 (Sub-series 2, Box 5, Folder 4)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, July 14 through July 31, 1919. 7 items., id62037 (Sub-series 2, Box 5, Folder 5)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, August 1919. 11 items, id62039 (Sub-series 2, Box 5, Folder 6)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, September 1 through September 18, 1919. 8 items., id62040 (Sub-series 2, Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead., id62041 (Sub-series 2, Box 6)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, September 19 through September 30, 1919. 8 items., id62042 (Sub-series 2, Box 6, Folder 1)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, October 1 through October 16, 1919. 12 items., id62043 (Sub-series 2, Box 6, Folder 2)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, October 17 through October 31, 1919. 14 items., id62044 (Sub-series 2, Box 6, Folder 3)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, November, 1919. 12 items., id62045 (Sub-series 2, Box 6, Folder 4)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, December, 1919. 8 items., id62046 (Sub-series 2, Box 6, Folder 5)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, January, 1920. 10 items., id62047 (Sub-series 2, Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, February through March 1920. 10 items., id62048 (Sub-series 2, Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead., id62049 (Sub-series 2, Box 7)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, February, March and April, 1920. 12 items., id62050 (Sub-series 2, Box 7, Folder 1)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, April through May, 1920. 7 items., id62051 (Sub-series 2, Box 7, Folder 2)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, June through July, 1920. 14 items., id62052 (Sub-series 2, Box 7, Folder 3)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, August through September, 1920. 12 items., id62053 (Sub-series 2, Box 7, Folder 4)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, October through December, 1920. 10 items., id62054 (Sub-series 2, Box 7, Folder 5)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, 1921. 10 items., id62055 (Sub-series 2, Box 7, Folder 6)
        - Letters from Ruth Conkey to Champ Armistead, 1922. 6 items., id62056 (Sub-series 2, Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Cary Armistead Correspondence. Correspondence related to personal business (finances, property) and friendly communication., id62057 (Sub-series 2, Box 8)
        - Correspondence Between Cary and Julia Armistead. 20 items., id62058 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal Business, Undated. 11 items., id62059 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 2)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal Business, 1885 to 1889. 23 items., id62060 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal Business, 1890 to 1892. 33 items., id62061 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal Business, 1893 to 1895. 17 items., id62062 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 5)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal Business, 1896 to 1897. 26 items., id62063 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 6)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal Business, 1898 to 1901. 19 items., id62064 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 7)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal, 1888 to 1892. 32 items., id62065 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 8)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal, 1893 to 1896. 11 items., id62066 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Personal, 1897 to 1901. 14 items., id62067 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 10)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Favor Requests, undated. 6 items., id62068 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 11)
        - Cary Armistead Correspondence – Favor Requests, 1884 to 1900. 24 items., id62069 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 12)
        - Letters from William and Mary President Benjamin Ewell to Cary Armistead. 9 items., id62070 (Sub-series 2, Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Cary Armistead Correspondence., id61614 (Sub-series 3)
    - Family Correspondence. Armistead Family Letters and Correspondence, id61615 (Sub-series 4)
  - Other Family Materials, id61617
    - Armistead Family Education and Teaching Materials., id62072 (Box 10)
      - Armistead Children Report Cards. 8 items., id62176 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Dora (II) and Cara Armistead’s Teaching Materials. 16 items., id62177 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Cary Armistead’s Notes for 1878 Law Class. 2 items., id62179 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Dora (II) Armistead’s Homework. 21 items, id62180 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Champ Armistead’s Homework. 8 items., id62181 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Armistead Children Homework and Class Notes. 4 items., id62182 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - C. 1850 Spelling Book. 1 item., id62183 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Jefferson High School (Roanoke) 1926 Yearbook and Class of 1918 Clipping. 2 items., id62184 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Armistead Family Social, Cultural, and Property Materials., id62073 (Box 11)
      - Plats, Lease Contracts and Other Paperwork for the Pine Crest Subdivision of Williamsburg. 17 items., id62156 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Sales Paperwork for the Lot Next to the Armistead Lot. 2 items., id62157 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Documents Relating to Fuel Oil Rationing in Colonial Williamsburg Area Homes, 1944. 5 items., id62158 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper Clippings Related to Colonial Williamsburg, including W.A.R. Goodwin, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., and Henry Ford. 3 items., id62159 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Meriwether Armistead Office Space in Colonial Williamsburg, Leases and Other Documentation. 15 items., id62160 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence Between the Colonial Williamsburg Foundation and the Armistead Family. 2 items., id62161 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Contour Map of the Armistead Lot. 1 item., id62162 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Jamestown 350 Celebration – 1957 Information on Queen Elizabeth’s Visit. 6 items., id62163 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Confederate Memorial Lawsuit of 1932 – Legal Documents. 11 items., id62164 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Confederate Memorial Lawsuit of 1932 – Signed Relocation Petition. 1 item., id62165 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Confederate Memorial Lawsuit of 1932 – Clippings and Letters. 4 items., id62166 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Commencement Invitations. 6 items., id62168 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - William and Mary-Related Materials – Bulletins, Newsletters, Fraternity Letters. 15 items., id62169 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - William and Mary Event Programs. 5 items., id62170 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - October 14, 1934 Virginia Gazette. 2 items., id62171 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Plat of the Keck Farm, James City County. 2 items., id62172 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Rental Agreement Between Cary Armistead and H.L. Hundley. 1 item, id62174 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - The Application of Hallie Sinclair English Oliver for Membership in the Daughters of the American Revolution. 1 item., id62175 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Armistead Family Issues and Interests. Issues included here are church materials, politics, the Travis House, collected advertising materials, seed and bulb advertisements, Cara’s contest entries, Dora (I)’s family tree, and pro- and anti-Ku Klux Klan clippings., id62075 (Box 13)
      - Cary Armistead Church Materials – Correspondence, 1885 to 1894. 12 items., id62115 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Cary Armistead Church Materials – Correspondence, 1895 to 1901. 20 items., id62116 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Cary Armistead Church Materials – Finance. 18 items., id62117 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Cary Armistead Church Materials – Printed Materials. 29 items., id62118 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Correspondence, Undated. 6 items., id62119 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Correspondence, 1884 to 1890. 10 items., id62120 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Correspondence, 1891 to 1899. 16 items., id62121 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Vote Tallies and Committee Lists. 12 items., id62122 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Senate Bills and City Ordinances. 5 items., id62123 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Campaign Materials. 10 items., id62124 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Democratic Ticket Cards. 21 items., id62125 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Speeches. 2 items., id62126 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Cary Armistead Politics – Certificate of Appointment to the Williamsburg Precinct Committee for the 1892 Presidential Election. 1 item., id62127 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Menu and Correspondence Related to the Travis House. 5 items., id62128 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous Collected Advertising Materials. 22 items., id62129 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous Collected Advertising Materials. 26 items., id62130 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Cara Armistead’s Newspaper and Magazine Contest Entries. 34 items., id62131 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Cara Armistead’s Seed and Bulb Advertisements. 25 items., id62132 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Dora (I) Armistead – Jones and Tinsley Family Trees. 2 items., id62133 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Pro- and Anti-Ku Klux Klan Clippings Sent from Champ to Dora (I) Armistead. 3 items., id62134 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Photographs. Note that, when possible, the photographs have been removed from the original folder, envelope or sleeve. When done, the original folder or sleeve has been filed with its accompanying photograph. These items are included in the item total for each folder (i.e., one photograph and its accompanying folder are considered two items)., id62076 (Box 14)
      - Photos of William Junell, Francis Stevens, John Wear and an Unidentified Male, Posing in Front of a Statue of Thomas Jefferson on the Campus of the University of Virginia. 12 items., id62100 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Undated Portrait Proofs of Meriwether Armistead. 5 items., id62101 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Portraits – Two of Champ Armistead, One of Champ, Gregory and Meriwether Armistead. 6 items., id62102 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified Portraits. 8 items., id62103 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Portraits of Family Friends. 4 items., id62104 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Portraits of Armistead Family Members – One Possibly Cary, One Possibly Col. Robert H. Armistead, One of Family. 5 items., id62105 (Box 14, Folder 6)